Harding Black collection, Inclusive: 1910-2014, undated, Bulk: 1954-1998, undated
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Collected Papers, 1953-2014; 2
  - Electronic Media: "Harding Black: An American Treasure," VHS: (2 of 2), 1995 (Box 15 OVZ, Folder 8)
  - Electronic Media: KWTX/KCTF Artist Harding Black, VHS, circa 1995 (Box 15 OVZ, Folder 9)
  - Electronic Media: KWTX Artist Harding Black, VHS, circa 1995 (Box 15 OVZ, Folder 10)
  - Electronic Media: Harding Black, KLRN-PBS, VHS: (1 of 3), circa 1995 (Box 15 OVZ, Folder 11)
  - Electronic Media: Harding Black, KLRN-PBS, VHS: (2 of 3), circa 1995 (Box 16 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Electronic Media: Harding Black, KLRN-PBS, VHS: (3 of 3), circa 1995 (Box 16 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Electronic Media: Paul Hatgil Interview, VHS, 1998 January 24 (Box 16 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - Electronic Media: Richard Lincoln Interview, VHS, 1998 January 27 (Box 16 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - Electronic Media: Richard Lincoln Interview, DVD-R: (1 of 2), 1998 January 27 (Box 16 OVZ, Folder 20)
  - Electronic Media: Richard Lincoln Interview, DVD-R: (2 of 2), 1998 January 27 (Box 16 OVZ, Folder 21)
  - Electronic Media: Charles Long Interview, VHS, 1998 February 24 (Box 16 OVZ, Folder 5)
  - Electronic Media: Charles Long Interview, DVD-R: (1 of 2), 1998 February 24 (Box 16 OVZ, Folder 22)
  - Electronic Media: Charles Long Interview, DVD-R: (2 of 2), 1998 February 24 (Box 16 OVZ, Folder 23)
  - Electronic Media: Georgia Gough Interview, VHS, 1998 March 3 (Box 16 OVZ, Folder 6)
  - Electronic Media: Georgia Gough Interview, DVD-R: (1 of 2), 1998 March 3 (Box 16 OVZ, Folder 24)
  - Electronic Media: Georgia Gough Interview, DVD-R: (2 of 2), 1998 March 3 (Box 16 OVZ, Folder 25)
  - Electronic Media: Carroll Simms Interview, VHS, 1999 March 8 (Box 16 OVZ, Folder 7)
  - Electronic Media: Carroll Simms Interview, Part #1, DVD-R: (1 of 2), 1999 March 8 (Box 16 OVZ, Folder 26)
  - Electronic Media: Carroll Simms Interview, Part #1, DVD-R: (2 of 2), 1999 March 8 (Box 16 OVZ, Folder 27)
  - Electronic Media: Carroll Simms Interview, Part #2, DVD-R: (1 of 2), 1999 March 8 (Box 16 OVZ, Folder 28)
  - Electronic Media: Carroll Simms Interview, Part #2, DVD-R: (2 of 2), 1999 March 8 (Box 16 OVZ, Folder 29)
  - Electronic Media: Harding Black website materials, CD-R, 2008 August 27 (Box 16 OVZ, Folder 30)
  - Electronic Media: Harding Black website materials, CD-R, circa 2008 (Box 16 OVZ, Folder 31)
  - Electronic Media: Harding Black memorial disc, DVD-R, undated (Box 16 OVZ, Folder 32)
  - Electronic Media: Horse photographs, CD-R, 2015 (Box 16 OVZ, Folder 33)
  - Electronic Media: Selected photographs from Harding Black collection, CD-R, circa 2011 (Box 16 OVZ, Folder 34)